# SHAWN JOSEPH WORDPRESS & SHOPIFY EXPERT

Star Gate, Airport, Karachi, Pakistan +92-3112-900737 sj961440@gmail.com

## **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY:**

Leveraging my **2+ years of experience**, I excel in crafting high-performing websites on WordPress and Shopify platforms. My expertise encompasses a diverse range of themes and plugins, enabling me to deliver responsive, visually compelling, and optimized solutions.

#### **SKILLS:**

**7** React

Shopify

Web performance optimization

# **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

# WordPress & Shopify Developer

ANH Group Mar, 2023 - Aug, 2024



- Customized WordPress and Shopify themes according to requirements,
- Enhance the speed of the website for a great user experience.
- Upload Products on both CMS platforms.
- Have a great knowledge of Elementor and WP Bakery Page Builder.
- Implement Additional CSS as per requirement.

#### Web Developer (Remote)

Zeetek Services May, 2024- July 2024



- Customized WordPress and Shopify themes according to requirements.
- Convert PSD to HTML/WordPress
- Work on HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Build Site by using Elementor and WP Bakery Page Builder.
- Enhance the speed of the website for a great user experience.
- Upload Products on WordPress and Shopify.
- Implement Additional CSS as per requirement.

## **WordPress Developer (Remote)**

Image Impact

Fed, 2024- May, 2024



- · Customized WordPress themes according to requirements,
- Enhance the speed of the website for a great user experience.
- Upload Products on WordPress.
- Build Site by using Elementor and WP Bakery Page Builder.
- Implement Additional CSS as per requirement.

## WordPress & Shopify Intern

Dapytech Aug, 2022 - Jan 2023



- Work on WordPress and Shopify themes and plugins.
- Work on Elementor.
- Create dropshipping Shopify stores.
- Upload products on WordPress and Shopify.
- Implement Additional CSS as per requirement.

#### **React Intern (Remote)**

Tech Flickers

Jan, 2021 - Mar 2021



- Developed a dynamic and responsive front-end webpage using React.
- Work with API's.
- Coordinate with backend developers.

# **EDUCATION:**

# **Bachelor of Commerce (B.Com)**

University Of Karachi July, 2021 - Present

#### Complete Inter In Commerce (I.COM)

Superior Govt College, Karachi, Pakistan May, 2018 - Aug 2020

## **Complete Matriculation**

Airport Grammar School, Karachi, Pakistan April, 2018

# **CERTIFICATE**

# **Front End Web Development**

Tech Pakistan Oct 2020

## **MY PROJECTS:**

https://drive.google.com/file/d/1iZ7FTmgZTBrlprXZVNZ
 iU\_ufWIW3mOwU/view?usp=sharing